<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NASA (@nasa) - Instagram</title>
    <link>https://www.instagram.com/nasa/</link>
    <description>&lt;img src=https://s2.imginn.com/531774345_18540287185049152_7874995044152401858_n.jpg?t51.2885-15/531774345_18540287185049152_7874995044152401858_n.jpg?stp=dst-jpg_e15_fr_p1080x1080_tt6&amp;_nc_ht=scontent-hou1-1.cdninstagram.com&amp;_nc_cat=104&amp;_nc_oc=Q6cZ2QEBbT6xvgeKLUoecFXdhGds1oqJBiqcAd4Q_ThwYtYK60cOLd931c8SLmS8k0Qa1514QcGIt2f5I28Q0RhJKyDc&amp;_nc_ohc=SKvxLxn_MC8Q7kNvwEJXmQ6&amp;_nc_gid=5FCMA7elUacLc84WLDr-1g&amp;edm=APU89FABAAAA&amp;ccb=7-5&amp;ig_cache_key=MzY5NzY2MDk2OTgzMjgwODA4NA%3D%3D.3-ccb7-5&amp;oh=00_AfdTmGCIny6gq_jtaHMtwQ8maK2vDpE92b9OYCDmvN5imw&amp;oe=69014E37&amp;_nc_sid=bc0c2c&amp;dl=1/&gt; Instagram posts from @nasa</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:52:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Under the sea🪸⁣ ⁣In 2020, @NASAHubble released this image, nicknamed the “Cosmic Reef,” to celebrate</title>
      <link>https://imginn.com/p/DNQuxufAih9/</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="https://s2.imginn.com/531774345_18540287185049152_7874995044152401858_n.jpg?t51.2885-15/531774345_18540287185049152_7874995044152401858_n.jpg?stp=c0.135.1080.1080a_dst-jpg_e35_s640x640_sh0.08_tt6&amp;_nc_ht=scontent-hou1-1.cdninstagram.com&amp;_nc_cat=104&amp;_nc_oc=Q6cZ2QEBbT6xvgeKLUoecFXdhGds1oqJBiqcAd4Q_ThwYtYK60cOLd931c8SLmS8k0Qa1514QcGIt2f5I28Q0RhJKyDc&amp;_nc_ohc=SKvxLxn_MC8Q7kNvwEJXmQ6&amp;_nc_gid=5FCMA7elUacLc84WLDr-1g&amp;edm=APU89FABAAAA&amp;ccb=7-5&amp;ig_cache_key=MzY5NzY2MDk2OTgzMjgwODA4NA%3D%3D.3.c-ccb7-5&amp;oh=00_AfdBrsl2GNr-gEgQwBM3rOQbMEIYiKUCd0RGJ5cSJV97PA&amp;oe=69014E37&amp;_nc_sid=bc0c2c" alt="Instagram post"/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Under the sea🪸⁣ ⁣In 2020, @NASAHubble released this image, nicknamed the “Cosmic Reef,” to celebrate 30 years in space. It shows a giant red nebula and its smaller blue neighbor, which are both part of a vast star-forming region in the Large Magellanic Cloud, a satellite galaxy of the Milky Way, located 163,000 light-years away. In this picture, we can see how young, energetic, massive stars illuminate and sculpt their birthplace with powerful winds and searing ultraviolet radiation.⁣ ⁣At the heart of the big red nebula are sparkling stars, each of which are 10 to 20 times more massive than our Sun. The stars' ultraviolet radiation heats the surrounding dense gas. The massive stars also unleash fierce winds of charged particles that blast away lower-density gas, forming the bubble-like structures seen on the right, which resemble coral.⁣ ⁣By contrast, the seemingly isolated blue nebula at lower left was created by a solitary mammoth star 200,000 times brighter than our Sun. The blue gas was ejected by the star through a series of eruptive events during which it lost part of its outer envelope of material.⁣ ⁣Image description: An image is split in two. In the bottom left of the first image a bright blue ring appears, slightly fading in all directions, with a small blue dot in the middle. Red and orange waves of gas ripple, arcing from top left to top right. A light blue center appears out of the sea of red, and several bright white dots shine through. In the top right, dark blue gas emanates from the blackness of space.⁣Credit: NASA, ESA, STScI⁣ ⁣#NASA #Hubble #CoralReef #Nebula #Stars #Astronomy</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.instagram.com/p/DNQuxufAih9/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
